export const MathMedium=[
  {
    question: "Find the sum of 111 +222 + 333",
    Options: ["700", "666", "10", "100"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Subtract 457 from 832",
    Options: ["375", "57", "376", "970"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "50 times 5 is equal to",
    Options: ["2500", "505", "500", "None of these"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "90 รท 10",
    Options: ["9", "10", "900", "1"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Simplify: 26 + 32 - 12",
    Options: ["0", "32", "56", "46"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Find the product of 72 ร 3",
    Options: ["216", "7230", "106", "372"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Solve : 200 - (96รท4)",
    Options: ["105", "176", "26", "16"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Solve : 24+4+4",
    Options: ["25", "6", "28", "7"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Simplify: 3 + 6 x (5 + 4) + 3-7",
    Options: ["11", "16", "14", "15"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Simplify :150รท(6 + 3 x 8) - 5",
    Options: ["2", "5", "0", "None of these"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are there in 1000?",
    Options: ["One digit", "Two digits", "Three digits", "Four digits"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Complete the sequence 13, 16, 22.",
    Options: ["17", "18", "19", "20"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the largest two digits prime number?",
    Options: ["96", "97", "98", "99"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "1 dime = dollar",
    Options: ["0.20", "10", "0.10", "0.01"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How many factors are there in 71?",
    Options: ["1", "2", "3", "None of these."],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the largest number in 15/17, 15/18, 15/19, 15/21?",
    Options: ["15/17", "15/18", "15/19", "15/21"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the average value of 25, 20, 23 and 22?",
    Options: ["20", "21.5", "22.5", "24"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "2 is a number.",
    Options: ["Odd", "Prime", "Composite", "None of these."],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the sum of one digit prime numbers?",
    Options: ["11", "13", "15", "17"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How many hours in 120 minutes?",
    Options: ["2 hours", "30 hours", "1 hour", "None of these."],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  }
]
